This is not my body.
These are not my hands.
Dad!
Dad, I told you
to stay in the car!
Why didn'Őt you stay in the car?
This is not my son.
Dad?
This is not my body.
Hey, sleeping beauty.
My mom'Ős traveling
from Cape Town next month.
And if you Don'Őt wake up...
She'Ős gonna smack you awake.
"And in the aftermath,
she thought of all the times
they had been there...
Together.
And the promises they made.
No matter where we are
in the world...
However strange or distant,
however far...
Or impossible...
However cruel
or painful...
I promise you, I will never die,
unless i'Őm looking
into your eyes."
Three months.
Three months in a coma!
Are we gonna do this daily?
What happened to Sebastian?
How does a fucking drone pilot
land up in a coma?
Tell me why I shouldn'Őt
fucking kill you!
Because you'Őre not stupid.
Get in the car.
It'Ős on me, what happened.
If I could explain it, I would.
Let'Ős get you home.
Who'Ős this?
We got a problem here?
You all right?
Who'Ős she?
Alexa.
Sebastian'Ős Alexa.
What'Ős going on?
They won'Őt tell me anything.
I have a family, please.
I'Őve never harmed
another person before
in my life.
Who are you?
Call harmon.
Yeah, about that...
Senator John harmon,
chair of
the armed services committee,
was fatally stabbed today
by a longtime aide
who says he has no memory
of the attack.
What is this? What'Ős happening?
Everyone, get in the car.
Yeah, I Don'Őt work for you.
You do now.
This is not a good idea.
Where are we?
Someplace safe.
You really think
she can handle this?
What'Ős this?
Subject of my postdoc thesis.
Well, plus my
hawkings-level brilliance.
Just put her in.
You ready?
If you want answers
about Sebastian,
you'Őve gotta put this on.
Step into the tub.
Oh, hell no.
I worked with Sebastian too.
I promise
it will all make sense.
It'Ős the only way
to get him back.
The ice will numb you
and help you let go.
Mm-hmm.
Just remember these words:
"This is not my body."
This is not my body?
"This is not my body," say it.
This is not my body.
Wait!
Hello?
Who are you?
This is not your hand.
This is not your body.
What did you do to me? It'Ős all right.
What the fuck did you do
to my hand?
Your hand is fine.Relax.
We just digitally mapped
your consciousness
into another person'Ős body.
You told me that he was
a drone pilot.
This is the future
of drone warfare.
If you can'Őt get
to someone, we can.
We kill the bad guys.
Somebody else takes the fall.
It'Ős just that simple.
This is crazy.
This is sanctioned?
Do you remember
the midway shooter?
The police couldn'Őt get close.
Yeah, his sister killed him.
Her finger was on the trigger,
but Sebastian was
controlling that finger.
This is Adrian delorio,
the fixer'Ős fixer.
He can smuggle
the obamas into China
and an entire cartel
into Texas completely unnoticed.
This is Adrian'Ős crypto guy,
who can make millions
disappear and reappear.
Except, it wasn'Őt him at all.
Sebas... Sebastian?
He was in about a week.
Adrian must have sensed
something.
Wha... what'Ős he doing?
Stealing my tech.
It'Ős completely untraceable.
Burrows right
into the brain stem.
So what happened to Sebastian?
What happens when
it gets pulled out like that?
It'Ős like a file transfer
that crashes mid-download.
Gets corrupted.
So will he ever wake up?
If you can get
that spider back, yes.
It won'Őt matter
if we'Őre all dead.
Adrian'Ős coming for us.
All of us.
So you'Őre hiding. No.
We'Őre hunting.
So how does this work?
The brain is just
an electrical system,
and any system can be hacked.
Sorry.
That is your drone.
And this is your target.
How do I come home?
You close your eyes.
You feel yourself,
your real self.
It'Ős been there all along.
Then you say the words
you know are true.
This is not my body.
First, the occipital lobe.
Then sight.
Then sound.
Then the limbic system.
Motor control.
And last...
Feelings.
Your mind screams. It resists.
So you remind it,
"this is not my body."
Who is he? Do
you really wanna know?
I'Őm about to kill a stranger
in another person'Ős body.
I want to know.
He'Ős Adrian'Ős transport guy.
Traffics underage girls
out of Morocco.
We take down Adrian'Ős crew.
We flush him out.
We find the tech.
And then I kill him?
This is not my body!
This doesn'Őt feel right.
He was a bad guy.
You'Őve killed bad guys.
Yeah. Not like that,
I haven'Őt.
Do you know how many soldiers
i'Őve sent to Iraq
so we could live?
Nobody has to be sent anymore.
You have plenty of other
people that can do this.
I do,
but I can'Őt trust them. Why?
Adrian could be
any of 'Őem by now.
Now, make this work.
Olivia.
Olivia! Hey, Olivia.
Why am I pregnant?
Hey. Why am I pregnant?
What'Ős happened?
It'Ős memory contamination.
You were just a pregnant woman.
I can feel it kicking.
Pull it the fuck together.
I got this! Back off.
No. What? Oh, my god.
Hey, you can'Őt be them
without feeling what they feel.
That'Ős physical sensations,
emotional states.
Okay. Yeah. I need
you to make it stop.
I can'Őt.Please.
Oh, my god.
What am I gonna do?
Here. Do you feel that?
There'Ős nothing there.
You'Őre not her.
It'Ős you in your body.
What?
I'Őm not...
Huh? Huh?
So do they know?
Do the hosts know
what we'Őve done to them?
Mmm. No. When you'Őre inside,
it'Ős like they'Őre disconnected
from everything we think of
as consciousness.
It'Ős like sleep, but no dreams.
You can stop touching me now.
Sorry.
She is a mess.
You never should have
brought her here.
She'Őll be fine. Fine?
Sebastian lasted months
before his memory contamination.
How long does she have?
Who the fuck cares? Get
her the fuck out of here.
Not gonna happen.
Then i'Őm leaving. You leave, you die.
He'Őll find you.
He'Őll get inside your head.
He'Őll know everything you know.
Find a way to believe in her.
Who'Ős first?
We call him Mr. Bubblegum.
Your drone is Mali saman.
She'Ős an artist.
Mr. Bubblegum'Ős her agent.
He likes showing her off.
Why are we targeting bubblegum?
Bubblegum is selling
Mali'Ős paintings to Adrian.
Get close to Adrian.
None of that
eat-the-rich shit today.
All you gotta do is tell him
how good your work looks
in his house
so he can close that deal.
Got it?
Okay.
Take your shoes off.
You too.
Happy?
What do you think?
Good right here?
Looks like crap there.
Well, where do you want it?
Wherever the fuck
he'Ős gonna pay the most for it.
Show me the hallway.
Sure.
That'Ős my favorite.
Hi. Adrian.
Towels!
Stay calm.
He doesn'Őt know who you are.
Oof.
The towels.
Oh, I should get someone. No!
Uh, can you just, um,
help take them out?
Uh, sure.
Gun. Glass.
And...
This one'Ős gonna hurt.
Two.
You okay?
Mmm.
All right.
So let'Ős keep the pain away
from that mind of yours.
Tell me about that painting.
I just paint.
Uh, toddlers paint.
Your painting'Ős
a lot more refined.
I'Őm not good at describing it.
Well, try.
"All my life,
I dreamed beneath the sea,
and I looked upon the surface.
Till one day I crashed
into the surface
and looked upon the sea."
It'Ős a line
from a book I was reading
while I was creating.
Can I tell you something?
I mistook you
for a complete stranger.
But we have a lot more
in common than I thought.
We both know that
web of humanity is
the best book on the planet.
And that'Ős from a guy
who hates love stories.
Uh, how is it a love story?
How is it not?
It'Ős revenge. Pure and simple.
Well, for someone
who recited so eloquently
from what is clearly
one of her favorite books...
Maybe you'Őre missing
the poetry of it.
"I gazed and gazed
until the surface became
a reflection.
Neither sea nor sky
a reflection of itself."
Well, I hate poetry.
What? Why?
You'Őre an artist.
You Don'Őt know anything
about me.
Well, tell me about you.
I bought that book
for someone I love.
We were gonna read it together.
We never got the chance to.
And i'Őm not sure we ever will.
What happened to him?
Something I wouldn'Őt wish
upon my worst enemy.
Well, let'Ős drink to that.
Cheers.
Mali? Mali?
Are you okay?
You Don'Őt look okay.
What are you doing?
You weren'Őt coming back.
I was worried about you.
I pulled you back.
I was with him! What?
Adrian.
Put me back in! Now!
How did I...
You okay?
Yeah, I, uh...
I get dizzy spells sometimes.
It'Ős...
It'Ős probably the blood.
I'Őm fine.
Hey, what'Ős up? Sorry.
No, it'Ős fine.
You kill him,
his network goes underground,
and he loses our tech.
I'Őm sorry to hear that.
How can I help?
This guy lives in the shadows.
He could disappear at any
second and be gone for years.
Find a way to keep him close.
Great.
See you tomorrow.
Hey, boss.
Oh, uh, my apologies.
I... I have to go.
Take care of that foot.
Wait!
You just bought
my entire collection.
And I Don'Őt sell just to anyone.
I'Őd love to get
to know you more
or the deal'Ős off.
Mmm.
I'Őll send a car at 4:00.
Ow.
There you are.
When did this happen?
Wait, did you let me
drink again?
Alexa,
Adrian knows we'Őre on to him.
Kill everyone
that can help him disappear.
I'Őll find someone
to take the blame for you.
Trust me, you'Őre not gonna
find a better lawyer
in this town.
Tell those kids
not to touch my car.
Hey.
Sorry.
Okay, I gotta go. Hey, wait!
I think I lost my key.
Would it be underneath your car?
It'Ős done.
I'Őve checked the cameras.
Lay low. I'Őll be in touch.
This is not my body.
This is not my body!
It'Ős time to see Adrian.
You good?
This is not my body.
What do you think?
I think I still can'Őt
believe this is your home.
Still much more of
a house than a home.
Oh, i'Őd love to see
the rest of it.
Isn'Őt it beautiful?
I'Őd love to settle down
here someday,
with the right person,
of course.
I have a
web of humanity story too.
Someone wanted to share it
with me.
But at the time, I didn'Őt know
how to share anything with her.
Anyway, one day, I woke up
and realized she had no idea
who I was.
I mean, she had a version of me,
but I wasn'Őt that person
anymore.
So I walked, and of course,
the moment I walked,
I started to miss her.
But I found her again
in the book.
Saw her on every page.
Saw all the reasons why
she wanted to share it with me.
And I fell in love with her
all over again.
I see it as a love story.
A love story
I can never get back.
I can relate.
I like being here with you.
Are you okay?
Uh, too much for a first date?
I, um...
I didn'Őt think this was a date.
Sorry, I misread it.
No, um, I just have to leave.
She should be back by now.
It'Ős taking too long.
Hey, you'Őve reached Mali.
Leave a message.
Pull her out.
It'Ős not working.
Something'Ős wrong.
She looks tired. Not "she."
You. Alexa.
Alexa'Ős just a body.
Don'Őt!
It would break you to feel
both at the same time.
I Don'Őt even know
what would happen.
He could have followed you here.
It'Ős time to go.
I can'Őt.
I Don'Őt know how.
I kept hearing my own voice.
Seeing my own skin.
I kept saying the words,
but it didn'Őt...
It didn'Őt work.
I couldn'Őt come back, so I...
I came back here.
Whatever you'Őre feeling
right now, use it.
Remember who you are.
You'Őre here. You see it.
Now, find your way back.
What would he do...
When it got like this?
Sebastian?
He would go home to you.
It'Ős time to go.
You got two hours to come home,
or i'Őll pull the fucking plug.
Hey, you'Őve reached Mali.
Leave a message.
Let'Ős go for a drive.
Hello.
Hey, did we party last night?
No. You said you
were staying in.
Well, I Don'Őt
remember anything.
Where are you right now?
I Don'Őt know.
Come back to me.
What if I Don'Őt know how?
Then i'Őll
have to come find you.
What can I get you?
Grilled cheese with tomato.
Do you know what
they call that? A happy waitress?
A happy waitress.
And for the lady?
I'Őm not hungry.
Your husband
always ordered lobster.
At the diner.
Like an amateur.
He wasn'Őt an amateur.
You just didn'Őt know him.
I spent months in
the safe house with him.
Oh, yeah?
So why did he order
lobster then?
We were in Baghdad.
We got pinned down in
this bombed-out apartment,
and I was shaking in
my boots, and he was calm,
talking about...
"If we had to go out
to dinner tonight...
Where would you wanna go?
What would you wanna eat?"
And I just said,
"lobster."
And that was it.
For the rest of our
lives, he was always,
"someday, i'Őm gonna
take you out for lobster."
Why someday?
Because he was allergic
to shellfish.
Said he had to work up
tolerance.Amateur.
And he always fights for me.
For us.
And that'Ős why
this is really hard,
because I just
feel like he'Ős...
Gone.
Keep that connection.
These other bodies,
these other lives,
it'Ős just noise.
Tune it out.
You'Őll make it.
Need the bathroom.
A happy waitress, sunshine.
Hey, i'Őve been
looking all over for you.
Grilled cheese and tomato.
A happy waitress.
I'Őm happy, Mr. Valmora.
Are you happy too?
You enjoying the weather?
Get any bug bites lately?
It'Ős so nice to see you again.
You'Őre dead, you son of a
bitch. Only if you find me first.
Adrian got him.
Got me too.
He'Ős gonna use me now
to kill you.
You finish this.
I can already feel him
in my head.
Come on!
You'Őve always wanted this.
I'Őd do it.
How do I know you'Őre you?
You Don'Őt.
Well, they'Őre both dead,
and i'Őm going home.
You go home, Adrian wins.
Someone, some day,
is gonna put a knife
in your throat,
and you'Őre never
gonna see him coming.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Alexa, tomorrow, you see Adrian.
Tomorrow, you finish this.
Okay.
Come back to me.
Please.
I'Őm gonna do something
really hard now,
but...
I need you to hold me.
Who are you?
I'Őm... get out!
Oh, hi, Mali.
Was he expecting you?
What are you doing here?
I wanted to see you.
It'Ős not a good time.
What happened? Leave me alone!
What if I Don'Őt
wanna leave you alone?
Look, talk to me.
Just tell me where you are.
I ran into an old friend.
Didn'Őt go so well.
Me too.
What do you need right now?
If you want me to leave,
I can leave,
but I was hoping I could stay.
Sometimes, the only thing
that makes sense...
The only thing that
makes me feel like me
is... touch.
First, find the spider,
then you can kill him.
This is not my body.
What happened? I Don'Őt remember.
Why am I here? I pulled you out
when you lost consciousness.
Here. I Don'Őt need this.
You should change
out of your wet suit.
What are you talking about?
What the fuck?
I didn'Őt wanna get
you undressed. Who am I right now?
Who is standing in front of you?
Alexa.
Oh, god.
What happened in there?
Just tell me and we'Őll fix it.
You can'Őt fix it!
I can try.
Just come back.
I'Őm still her!
Who sent you?
Where the fuck am I?
What is it? Make it stop!
Please make it stop!
What is it? He disconnected me.
He disconnected me.
Fuck. What the fuck happened in there?
I found the tech.
I found Sebastian'Ős spider!
Fuck.
I'Őm calling the wet team.
He'Őll be dead in half hour.
Listen, Mali is in there.
I can'Őt let him kill her! What the fuck?
I'Őm gonna finish this.
Let me go! Help me!
This is not my body.
Alexa...
I love you.
Alexa!
Wait, I Don'Őt...
I Don'Őt understand.
Oh, I missed you. I missed you.
Hey.
Wait, I Don'Őt...
I saw you get shot.
You saw what
I wanted them to see.
Okay.
Why?
I couldn'Őt be
Sebastian anymore.
They broke me, Alexa.
Don'Őt you feel broken too?
They could turn off the machine,
but they couldn'Őt
disconnect me.
All the other lives
rattling around in my head.
Like a fire in my brain.
And the only way to put it out
was to stop being me.
If I could disappear,
if I could start over
as someone new...
I could be free.
I was never shot.
I was already Adrian.
I was finally free.
But they were never
gonna stop looking for me.
I had to take them out...
So that we could be free.
You must have felt that too,
when you were Mali.
Right? You...
You... you left me alone.
You almost fucking killed me!
I killed for you!
And you'Őve been running around
as Adrian,
chasing another woman!
I was grooming her for you,
so she could be your host!
So we could take
the tech and disappear! I Don'Őt want that.
Nobody could come
looking for us.
We can go wherever you wanna be.
Be whoever you wanna be!
I want to be Alexa!
I want you
to be Sebastian! Don'Őt call me that!
Alexa and Sebastian
are just bodies. Yeah, but it'Ős not...
We can be so much more! That'Ős not us!
That'Ős the whole point.
No, no. No!
Hey! Hey, hey, hey. No!
They used me. Don'Őt do this.
I did all the dirty work... Don'Őt do this!
And they got to
walk away clean! Don'Őt do this!
Hey! So we'Őre gonna walk away clean,
and you'Őre gonna be the one
that'Ős gonna suffer.
Please, Don'Őt do this!
Don'Őt do this, please!
Sebastian! Sebastian is gone!
"I promise you, i'Őll never die,
unless i'Őm looking
in your eyes."
Been months.
How are you holding up?
I, uh...
I Don'Őt know.
I'Őm... i'Őm fine.
It'Ős normal to have feelings.
You were her and now you'Őre...
You'Őre just you again.
Anyway, you hadn'Őt
checked in, so I...
I just wanted to make
sure you were okay.
I'Őm okay.
She'Ős gone missing.
You haven'Őt seen her, have you?
No.
Not a sight.
You hungry?
Hello, we all good in here?
I am drowning in here.
Can you take over?
Of course.
No, I mean take over.
I got you.
You have a beautiful family.
Me.
Your auntie.
And one day,
i'Őll tell you all about...
Your father.